https://www.asta-usa.com/privacy-statement-guarantees-and-policies/

Privacy Statement Guarantees And PoliciesRead ASTA-USA's Privacy Statement, Guarantees and Policies. ASTA-USA is a professional provider of translation services. Contact us today for a quote. ASTA-USA https://www.asta-usa.com/privacy-statement-guarantees-and-policies
Since 1987 Coronavirus Translations 1-866-446-1860
Toggle navigation
AboutTranslation ServicesBusiness DocumentsCorporate LegalOfficial DocumentsHealthcare/MedicalTechnicalCorporate FinancialLanguagesEnglishFrenchGermanPortugueseJapaneseSpanishItalianRussianChineseForeignSee all languages we supportProfessional TranslatorsQuality AssuranceConfidentialityBlogChinese TranslationCorporation Translation ServiceDocument TranslationMultilingual TranslationQuality and AccuracySpanish TranslationTranslation AuditTranslation ServicesTranslation TrendsLocations
Contact Info
Get Price InfoContact
Privacy Statement, Guarantees and PoliciesPRIVACY STATEMENTAt ASTA-USA, we are committed to respecting your privacy. We do not gather, store, process or manage your personal data in any way while you are visiting our website or relaying information to us for your written materials translation needs.  Since we do not gather, store, process or manage your personal data, the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) do not apply to the type of service we provide.  The following sets forth our information gathering and usage practices for information collected on www.asta-usa.com, and any other websites that are part of the ASTA-USA Translation Services, Inc. online presence.Information Gathered At This WebsiteWhen you visit www.asta-usa.com our website recognizes the type of browser you are using, the address of the Internet Service Provider you are using, the pages you visit at our site(s), and similar information. None of this information identifies you personally. ASTA-USA does not currently use “cookies” on its websites.When using certain elements such as “Contact Us” or any of the “Online Forms,” you may voluntarily provide us with names, addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers, e-mail addresses, and similar information.Internal Use Of InformationWe may use the information that you have voluntarily submitted to provide the products or services that you have requested, to send to you via e-mail or postal mail, price quotes, brochures, new product announcements that are related to the products or services that you have requested from us or other information that we feel may be of value to you, and for other similar business purposes. The information you voluntarily provide us will not be shared, stored or processed for any reason other than to provide information and services as you have requested.Sharing Of Information With Third PartiesASTA-USA does not share any information that you may provide with third parties.  ASTA-USA maintains control the information you provide only for the purpose of the services provided and only for the duration of said services.Opting OutWe do not use your e-mail information as part of any mass-mailing activities.  We will only e-mail you regarding the services you have inquired about.  You may at any time opt-out of receiving further communications via e-mail. If you would like to opt-out of receiving further communications through e-mail or postal mail following your inquiry or engagement with our company, please contact our Customer Service Department.Corrections And UpdatesYou can change or modify any information you have previously provided to us by contacting our Customer Service Department.Modifications of our policy From time to time, we may modify our Privacy Policy. Such modifications will be effective on the date that we post the modified Policy on our websites.Contact InformationIf you have any questions about this website Privacy Policy, or about this website in general, please contact our Customer Service Department.ASTA-USA Privacy StatementUse of this site signifies your acceptance of the terms and conditions.PRIVACY STATEMENT, GUARANTEES AND POLICIESASTA-USA Translation Services, Inc. (ASTA-USA – Translator) is committed to 100% customer satisfaction.We aim to provide superior language translation services to our clients in a courteous, ethical, and timely manner. We can deliver the premium skill levels at a reasonable cost. We take a personal interest in our clients and give them the service, value and attention we seek in our own relationships.Delivery And Shipping PoliciesASTA-USA and its team of accredited translators will provide translation services of a variety of documents, materials and files provided in either hard copies (mail or fax), electronic copies such as e-mail and secure web-server transfers, etc.ASTA-USA will maintain an active record of said documents, materials, and files, only for the duration of the services provided, and make every effort to complete translation of each document by the prearranged date(s) but shall not be responsible for damages or delays in completion caused by events beyond ASTA-USA and its Translators’ control including but not limited to acts of nature, requests for changes and/or additions by client, formatting errors by client, program incompatibility, security protocols causing delays, custom coding, and delays caused by client’s programs failing to properly deliver or accept the document in proper format.Method Of DeliveryElectronic relays (standard e-mail or client managed ftp system), Facsimile, US mail, Express parcel delivery.Format Of Delivery“MS Word” US Letter or US Legal size. Other methods of delivery can be arranged with our Project Managers and will be based on each client’s requirements and needs.WarrantiesASTA-USA warrants that (a) it will use reasonable best efforts in the performance the services; (b) that the services and deliverables will be of professional quality exceeding or conforming to generally accepted best professional practices which are standard for first class document translation within the translation services industry; (c) and that performance of the services does not and will not violate any applicable law, rule, or regulation.If any services performed or deliverables provided by ASTA-USA are determined by Client to be inaccurate or defective or otherwise not in accordance with the requirements of the applicable documentation supplied by Client, ASTA-USA agrees to correct such services or deliverables without charge to Client within a reasonable period of time after receiving notice thereof.Fees For ServicesFees and costs may vary depending on the complexity, volume and required Client’s turnaround time. Each case will be treated individually and payment terms for this level of service must be arranged with your ASTA-USA representative before work begins. Client agrees to pay ASTA-USA’s fees in accordance with the fee and terms of payment presented to Client at the onset of the engagement.Any payments for fees or costs not received by ASTA-USA according to the terms of the agreement will be deemed late and shall be subject to a 1.2 % per month late charge. Client agrees to be responsible for ASTA-USA’s costs in collecting late payments due from Client, including reasonable attorneys’ fees.Cancellation Or Withdrawal By ClientIf Client cancels or withdraws any portion of the translation project prior to ASTA-USA’s completion of the service(s), then, in consideration of ASTA-USA’s scheduling and/or performing said service(s) Client shall pay ASTA-USA the portion of the above fee represented by the percentage of total service(s) performed.Refund PolicyIf Client cancels or withdraws any portion of the translation – for any reason – prior to ASTA-USA having begun performance of service(s), Client will be entitled to a complete and immediate refund of the applicable fees. Refund shall be issued via check by mail or credit card refund according to the manner of payment received from Client at the time the order was confirmed.Client’s Review Of TranslationUpon receipt of the translation from ASTA-USA, Client shall promptly review it, and within 5 (five) business days after receipt shall notify ASTA-USA of any requested corrections or changes. ASTA-USA shall correct, at no cost to Client, any errors made by ASTA-USA.Changes By OthersASTA-USA shall have no responsibility whatever as to any changes in the translation made by persons other than ASTA-USA.ConfidentialityAll knowledge and information provided by Client for translation shall be considered confidential including information regarding the business and products of Client and all such information shall remain the intellectual property of client and will be held strictly confidential by ASTA-USA, and except as expressly authorized by Client in writing, shall not be divulged or published by ASTA-USA and shall not be authorized by ASTA-USA to be divulged or published by others. Confidential information for purposes of this paragraph shall not include the following:a. Information, which is or becomes available to the general public, provided the disclosure of such information did not result from a breach by ASTA-USA of this paragraph.b. Terminological glossary entries compiled by ASTA-USA in the course of ASTA-USA’s performance of the translation service(s) under this Agreement; provided, however, that Client and ASTA-USA may agree in writing that, upon payment by Client to ASTA-USA of an agreed-upon fee, such terminological glossary entries shall be the property of Client and shall be covered by the confidentiality provisions of this paragraph.Contact InformationIf you have any questions about this website Privacy Policy, Guarantees and Other Policies, or about this website in general, please contact our Customer Service Department.Any questions?Save some time, call us now.1.866.446.1860.Or click here toGet a Quote Our clients come to us for accuracy & speed They stay with us For the sublime level of service we offer.Privacy Statement Guarantees And Policies"Thanks for your very professional work, prompt service, and great rates!"B. Monty Maughan
FAA - Aviation Systems StandardsPrivacy Statement Guarantees And Policies"Finally, a translation company that not only says they are professional, but really are.
The documents you delivered are perfect.
They look amazing.
I have used many other translation companies but none have delivered like this."Brandy Lee
Cross To LightPrivacy Statement Guarantees And Policies"How can you be so fast and yet always perfectly accurate?
You have a very solid team of legal translators and you always make me look good!"Tim Pompa
Weil, Gotshal & Manges, LLPPrivacy Statement Guarantees And Policies"All this data - domestic and foreign now makes all the sense in the world... Thanks to your brilliant translators!"R. L. Coulier
Northrop GrummanPrivacy Statement Guarantees And Policies"Thanks again for another terrific job… You are the best!"Anne Catherine Savage
UBS Investment BankPrivacy Statement Guarantees And Policies"You are always on top of everything. The translation is perfect and the service is first class!"Ron Bar
CITIGROUPPrivacy Statement Guarantees And Policies"We received the translated document and it is an outstanding work product.
Your team did a magnificent job on an incredibly rapid turnaround time.
You have just won a long-time customer for the quality, timeliness and value you provided us in this time of need."Robert J. (Bob) Coullahan
Readiness Resource Group
Previous
Next ASTA-USAHomeAboutCase StudiesCorporate Translation ServicesCorporate ProgramsASTA-USA’s LocationsTranslation ServicesTranslation Services QualityBusiness Translation ServicesLegal Translation ServicesOfficial Translation ServicesMedical Translation ServicesTechnical Translation ServicesFinancial Translation ServicesInformationPartial Client ListWhat You Must KnowAll Industries ServedLanguages OfferedProfessional TranslatorsConfidentialityPayment OptionsFAQContact UsBy EmailBy Phone: 1.866.446.1860Translation Service QuotesTranslation Services Information
© 2000-2020 ASTA-USA Translation Services, Inc. All Rights Reserved
Privacy Statement, Guarantees & Policies Terms of Service
